export const questionsObject = {
  q1: {
    question: "How do you feel about spontaneity in plans?",
    answers: ["Love it", "Like it", "Neutral", "Dislike it", "Strongly dislike it"]
  },
  q2: {
    question: "What's your ideal weekend getaway?",
    answers: ["Adventurous camping", "Relaxing at a cozy cabin", "Exploring a new city", "Visiting family or friends", "Enjoying a quiet staycation"]
  },
  q3: {
    question: "How do you approach decision-making?",
    answers: ["Quickly and decisively", "After careful consideration", "Collaboratively with others", "By seeking advice from friends", "Indecisiveness is my middle name"]
  },
  q4: {
    question: "What's your communication style during disagreements?",
    answers: ["Direct and assertive", "Calm and diplomatic", "Patient and understanding", "Avoid confrontation", "Silent treatment"]
  },
  q5: {
    question: "How important is physical activity to you?",
    answers: ["Extremely important", "Fairly important", "Neutral", "Not very important", "I prefer a sedentary lifestyle"]
  },
  q6: {
    question: "Choose a movie genre for a cozy night in:",
    answers: ["Action-packed thriller", "Romantic comedy", "Thought-provoking drama", "Sci-fi or fantasy adventure", "Horror, the scarier, the better"]
  },
  q7: {
    question: "What's your preferred way to spend a Friday evening?",
    answers: ["Socializing at a lively bar", "Cooking a gourmet dinner at home", "Attending a cultural event or concert", "Watching movies or series marathon", "Catching up on sleep"]
  },
  q8: {
    question: "How do you handle stress?",
    answers: ["Tackle it head-on", "Take a step back and breathe", "Share concerns with a confidant", "Distract myself with activities", "Retreat and deal with it privately"]
  },
  q9: {
    question: "How would you describe your sense of humor?",
    answers: ["Sarcastic and witty", "Lighthearted and playful", "Dry and observational", "Slapstick and goofy", "I don't find humor important"]
  },
  q10: {
    question: "What's your approach to handling disagreements in a relationship?",
    answers: ["Open communication and compromise", "Giving each other space to cool off", "Seeking advice from friends or family", "Apologizing to keep the peace", "Avoiding confrontation at all costs"]
  },
  q11: {
    question: "What's your stance on pets?",
    answers: ["Love animals, must have pets", "Enjoy pets but not a necessity", "Neutral, could go either way", "Prefer not to have pets", "Strongly dislike pets"]
  },
  q12: {
    question: "Choose a vacation destination:",
    answers: ["Tropical beach paradise", "European historical cities", "Nature retreat in the mountains", "Cultural exploration in Asia", "Staycation at home"]
  },
  q13: {
    question: "How would you describe your socializing preferences?",
    answers: ["Extroverted, love large gatherings", "Sociable, enjoy smaller groups", "Balanced, comfortable in any setting", "Introverted, prefer one-on-one interactions", "Solitude is my preferred company"]
  },
  q14: {
    question: "What's your attitude towards personal growth and self-improvement?",
    answers: ["Constantly seeking self-improvement", "Open to personal growth opportunities", "Comfortable with who I am", "Prefer stability over change", "Change is unnecessary"]
  },
  q15: {
    question: "How do you spend your free time?",
    answers: ["Engaging in a hobby or creative pursuit", "Reading books or watching documentaries", "Attending social events and gatherings", "Relaxing and unwinding at home", "I'm always on the go, no time for free time"]
  },
  q16: {
    question: "What's your take on public displays of affection?",
    answers: ["Love them, the more, the better", "Enjoy a moderate amount", "Neutral, it depends on the context", "Dislike them, keep it private", "Absolutely against any PDA"]
  },
  q17: {
    question: "How important is it for partners to share similar political views?",
    answers: ["Extremely important, it defines compatibility", "Important, but not a deal-breaker", "Neutral, political views don't matter much", "Prefer partners with differing views", "I'd rather not discuss politics in a relationship"]
  },
  q18: {
    question: "Would you consider an open relationship?",
    answers: ["Open to the idea, if communicated well", "Open-minded but unsure if it would work", "Neutral, it depends on the individuals involved", "Prefer a monogamous relationship", "Strictly against any form of open relationship"]
  },
  q19: {
    question: "What's your stance on recreational drug use?",
    answers: ["Supportive, it's a personal choice", "Open-minded, occasionally indulging is fine", "Neutral, as long as it doesn't affect the relationship", "Disapprove, but can tolerate occasional use", "Strictly against any form of drug use"]
  },
  q20: {
    question: "How would you describe your everyday style?",
    answers: ["Casual and laid-back", "Classic and timeless", "Trendy and fashionable", "Edgy and experimental", "I don't pay much attention to my style"]
  },
  q21: {
    question: "What's your go-to outfit for a special occasion?",
    answers: ["Elegant dress or suit", "Smart casual with a touch of flair", "On-trend and attention-grabbing", "Unique and unconventional", "Whatever is clean and comfortable"]
  },
  q22: {
    question: "How do you feel about thrift shopping?",
    answers: ["Love finding unique treasures", "Enjoy it occasionally", "Neutral, it's not my first choice", "Prefer new, branded items", "Thrift shopping is not for me"]
  },
  q23: {
    question: "What's your opinion on matching outfits with your partner?",
    answers: ["Adorable, I love coordinating looks", "Occasionally, but not always", "Neutral, it depends on the situation", "Prefer individual styles", "Absolutely against matching outfits"]
  },
  q24: {
    question: "How do you feel about ex-partners remaining friends?",
    answers: ["Supportive, it shows maturity", "Open to it but with reservations", "Neutral, depends on the circumstances", "Uncomfortable, prefer no contact", "Absolutely against it"]
  },
  q25: {
    question: "Would you be comfortable sharing your phone passcode with your partner?",
    answers: ["Completely comfortable, transparency is key", "Open to it with trust established", "Neutral, depends on the relationship", "Uncomfortable, value personal privacy", "Absolutely against sharing passcodes"]
  },
  q26: {
    question: "Would you consider relocating for a long-term partner's job or career opportunity?",
    answers: ["Absolutely, it's a shared adventure", "Open to it, with careful consideration", "Neutral, depends on the situation", "Uncomfortable, prefer stability", "Absolutely against relocating for a partner's career"]
  }
};
